<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">F.Aen</string>
    <string name="lg">en</string>

    <!-- Home -->
    <string name="diagram">Diagram of progression</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="enter_category">enter a category</string>
    <string name="enter_value">enter a value</string>


    <!-- Parameters -->
    <string name="parameter">Parameter</string>
    <string name="General">General</string>
    <string name="Language">Language</string>
    <string name="Theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="Data">Data</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="importcsv">Import from CSV</string>
    <string name="exportcsv">Export to CSV</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear Cache</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="ctrl">Super Vision Parent</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="about">Terms of Service</string>

    <!-- CGU -->
    <string name="cgu_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="cgu_intro_title">1. Introduction</string>
    <string name="cgu_intro_content">1.1 These Terms and Conditions (hereinafter referred to as "Terms") govern the use of the customizable bank account management application (hereinafter referred to as "the Application") provided by [Your Name or Your Companys Name] (hereinafter referred to as "We" or "Our").\n"
        "1.2 By downloading, installing, or using the Application, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not use the Application.</string>
    <string name="cgu_usage_title">2. Use of the Application</string>
    <string name="cgu_usage_content">2.1 You are authorized to use the Application for personal and non-commercial purposes.\n"
        "2.2 You are responsible for the confidentiality of your account information and the activity that occurs under your account.\n"
        "2.3 You agree not to use the Application for illegal purposes or in a manner that violates the rights of third parties.</string>
    <string name="cgu_customization_title">3. Customization of the Application</string>
    <string name="cgu_customization_content">3.1 The Application allows you to customize the appearance by choosing themes, colors, and categories.\n"
        "3.2 All customizations are saved locally on your device and are not shared online.</string>
    <string name="cgu_data_collection_title">4. Data Collection and Storage</string>
    <string name="cgu_data_collection_content">4.1 The Application collects and stores locally the data you enter, such as transactions, categories, and customization preferences.\n"
        "4.2 No personal data is sent or stored online without your explicit consent.</string>
    <string name="cgu_security_title">5. Security</string>
    <string name="cgu_security_content">5.1 We are committed to implementing reasonable security measures to protect your data. However, you understand and accept that the security of transmitted or stored information cannot be guaranteed.\n"
        "5.2 We are not responsible for the loss, theft, or unauthorized disclosure of your data.</string>
    <string name="cgu_updates_title">6. Updates</string>
    <string name="cgu_updates_content">6.1 We reserve the right to update the Application at any time.\n"
        "6.2 You may be prompted to update the Application regularly.</string>
    <string name="cgu_responsibilities_title">7. Responsibilities</string>
    <string name="cgu_responsibilities_content">7.1 We are not responsible for direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or exemplary damages resulting from your use of the Application or any other claim related in any way to your use of the Application.\n"
        "7.2 You agree to indemnify and hold us, as well as our directors, officers, employees, and agents, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys fees, made by a third party due to or arising out of your use of the Application or your violation of these Terms.</string>
    <string name="cgu_changes_title">8. Modifications</string>
    <string name="cgu_changes_content">8.1 We reserve the right to modify these Terms at any time. The modifications will take effect upon their publication in the Application.\n"
        "8.2 We encourage you to regularly check these Terms to stay informed of any changes.</string>
    <string name="cgu_contact_title">9. Contact</string>
    <string name="cgu_contact_content">9.1 For any questions regarding these Terms, please contact us at faureleo123@gmail.com.\n"
        "By using the Application, you agree to these Terms. Thank you for reading them carefully.</string>
    <string name="cgu_last_update">Last update: November 29, 2023</string>
</resources>

